{
    "id": "aa230bd5fcc34c948400d222d533dbed",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We brought the food ………………. they supplied the drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "and",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was poor ………………. she was honest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "or",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We can go jogging ………………….. we can stay here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "People liked her ………………… she was honest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "because",
                "but",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will phone you ………………… I arrive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "while",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He told me ………………… he loved me ………………. it was a lie.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what, and",
                "that, but",
                "that, and"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is a problem …………………. solution has baffled even the experts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whom",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It is a question ...................... nobody can answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I stayed an extra night …………….. I could see more of Mumbai.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "so that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. you need help, just let me know.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}